<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<publicwhip>
	<regmem personid="uk.org.publicwhip/person/10001" membername="Diane Abbott" date="2021-12-13">
		<category type="1" name="Employment and earnings">
			<record>
				<item>Payments from the Guardian, Kings Place, 90 York Way, London N1 9GU, for articles:</item>
				<item>24 July 2020, received £100. Hours: 1 hr. (Registered 02 February 2021)</item>
				<item>19 October 2020, received £258.80. Hours: 1 hr 30 mins. (Registered 02 February 2021)</item>
				<item>18 March 2021, received £300 for contribution to an article. Hours: 1.5 hrs. (Registered 23 March 2021)</item>
				<item>5 May 2021, received £100 for an article published on 22 April 2021. Hours: 45 mins. (Registered 07 June 2021)</item>
				<item>24 November 2020, received £200 from the BBC, Portland Place, London W1A 1AA, for an appearance on Any Questions on 13 November 2020. Hours: 1.5 hrs. (Registered 08 February 2021)</item>
				<item>17 March 2021, received £18,450 from Viking Penguin, 20 Vauxhall Bridge Rd, London SW1V 2SA, via Blake Friedmann Literary, TV &amp; Film Agency Ltd, Ground Floor, 15 Highbury Place, London N5 1QP, by way of an advance for a book. Hours: 80 hrs to date. (Registered 24 March 2021)</item>
				<item>4 July 2021, received £400 from Operation Black Vote, 18A Victoria Park Square, Bethnal Green, London E2 9PB, for delivering a presentation on 12 May 2021. Hours: 2 hrs. (Registered 02 August 2021)</item>
			</record>
		</category>
		<category type="4" name="Visits outside the UK">
			<record>
				<item>
					Name of donor: GUBA Foundation
					<br>Address of donor: 459 Prince Regent Lane, London E16 3HX</br>
					<br>Estimate of the probable value (or amount of any donation): International flights £805.07; accommodation £1,461.05; GUBA Awards event ticket £365.39; total value £2,631.51</br>
					<br>Destination of visit: Accra, Ghana</br>
					<br>Dates of visit: 5-12 November 2021</br>
					<br>Purpose of visit: To participate in the GUBA Foundation Yaa Asantewaa Womens Empowerment Awards ceremony and meet other relevant civil society organisations.</br>
					<br>(Registered 16 November 2021)</br>
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
		<category type="8" name="Miscellaneous">
			<record>
				<item>Since December 2015, a trustee of the Diane Abbott Foundation, which works to excel and improve education. (Registered 26 October 2016)</item>
			</record>
		</category>
	</regmem>
</publicwhip>